javqt.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Videos Jav hd porn & hd 1080p | Jav QT

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.javqt.com

## How we collect and why we gather personal data?

The comment form will be collected, as well as the IP address of the visitor and the string of browser user agents to help detect spam. You can provide the Gravatar service with an anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) to see if you are using it.

### Media

When uploading images to the website. Website visitors can download and extract from images on the site any location data.

### Cookies

If you leave our site with a comment?. These are for your convenience so when you leave another comment, and you don’t have to fill in your details again. These cookies are going to last for a year. To determine whether your browser accepts cookies, we will set a temporary cookie. If you have a website account and log in. No personal information in this cookie. Will be discarded when your browser is closed.

We will also set up several cookies when you log in to save your login information and display choices on your screen. Login cookies last two days, and cookies last one year for screen options. Selecting “Remember Me” will keep your login for two weeks. If you have deleted the login cookies log out of your account. Another cookie is stored in your browser if you edit or publish an article.No personal data is provided in this cookie and displays the post ID of the article you have just written. After a day, it expires.

### The content embedded on other websites

Embedded materials (e.g., videos, images, and articles) in articles on this site. Content incorporated from other sites is included in the Just as if the other website visitor visited it.

These websites may collect data concerning you, use cookies, incorporate third-party tracking and monitor your interaction with embedded content and, if you have an account, follow your interaction with embedded content and are logged into the site.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

You agree to the use of the Service terms outlined in this Privacy Policy. Explain Everything acknowledges that  **EU**  individuals have the right to  **access**  the personal information/data that we maintain about them following  **applicable**  privacy regulations, such as the GDPR.

## How much time we keep your information

The comment and the metadata will if you leave a comment. This is so that, instead of holding a moderation queue, we can automatically recognize and approve any further comments. We also store personal information in your user profile for users who register on our website (if any). Every user can always view, edit or remove his / her personal information (unless his / her username cannot be changed). Administrators of the website can also see and delete that data.

## What rights you have over your data

Information we hold about you, including any information You provided us. You contributed to us. You can also ask us to delete any personal information that we hold about you. Does not include any data which we have an administrative, legal or security obligation to keep.

## Where we send your information

An automated spam detection service may check the visitor’s comments.

## Your contact information

“Personal Data” refers to any personal information, including a first, first, last, or any other physical address, emails, telephone number or contact details, at work or home, as specified in Article 4 of the EU General Data Protection Act. “Personal Data”

## Additional information

You agree to our privacy policy by using our website.

### How we protect your data

This policy (the “Data Protection and Privacy Policy”) explains which personal data concerning you we collect when you visit our website (the “Website”), when and why we collect the personal data, how we use them, the conditions of our disclosure to third parties, as well as how we secure the stored personal info.

### What are the infringement procedures?

The General Data Protection of the European Union defines a breach of personal data as a violation of security which leads to accidental or illegal destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized divulgation or access to personal data which are transmitted or stored.

### What third parties we receive data from

In some cases, if we are obliged by law or believe in our good faith that the action is necessary to respect the law or legal proceedings, protect and protect our rights or prevent misuse of our Services, or protect the personal data, we may use or disclose your Data to a third party.

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

Regulations of the Securities Industry. The securities industry and securities ownership are subject to new disclosure laws. Publicly owned enterprises must report in two reports by the officials, directors and principal shareholders (Defined as 10% or more of the owners stock of the company).

(Visited 1056 times, 3 visits today)
